http://www.simongillespie.com/privacy-policy

Internships/Work Experience
Privacy PolicySimon Gillespie LtdGeneral Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)Privacy PolicyDATA CONTROLLER:Simon Gillespie Ltd104 New Bond StreetLondonW1S 1SUWe may change this policy from time to time, in line with business requirements. You should check back with this page of our website and review this policy to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25th May 2018.HOW WE USE AND PROTECT DATA:This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you contact us or visit our website. We collect and process personal data in order to manage our relationship with you. We are committed to being transparent about how we collect and use that data, and to meeting our data protection obligations.Under the new GDPR rules, introduced on 25th May 2018, we consider that processing of data supplied by existing, future and potential, clients is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests of the business – except where such interests are overridden by your interests, fundamental rights and freedoms, as the data subject, which require protection of personal data, in particular where the data subject is a child.OUR COMMITMENT TO YOU:We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide certain information, by which you can be identified when using our services, then you may be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.THE DATA WE COLLECT:We collect and process the following information: your name, address (including email address) and other contact details, together with all other information relevant to the relationship between you and Simon Gillespie Ltd. We collect this information directly from you.WHY WE COLLECT THIS DATA:We require this information in order to understand your needs and to provide you with a better service, and for the following additional reasons:• to maintain internal record keeping;• to improve our products and services;• to send promotional emails about new products, services or other information which we think you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided; and/or• to contact you for market research purposes.WHO HAS ACCESS TO THIS DATA:We may share your information internally within our management team, where providing access to your data is necessary for the performance of their roles. We may also share this information with government authorities for legitimate purposes.KEEPING YOUR DATA SECURE:We are committed to ensuring that your information is kept secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and other security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, user name, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR DATA FOR:We will keep personal information for as long as is necessary for the purposes we collect it. In addition, there are laws and regulations which set minimum periods for the retention of such information. Depending upon our relationship with you, we may keep your personal information for a number of years after our relationship ends.WE DO NOT SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:We do not sell, trade, rent, distribute or lease your personal information to others. We may share general aggregated demographic information, which is not linked to any personal information which could identify you, for the purposes outlined above.YOUR RIGHTS, QUERIES or COMPLAINTS:You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us as soon as possible. We will promptly update any information found to be incorrect.If you do not wish us to hold any information on you, please email us with your request to be removed and we will ensure that your instructions are carried out.As a data subject, you have a number of rights which you can exercise in relation to the information we hold about you. These are covered by the Data Protection Act 1998. You can read more about these here:https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/is-my-information-being-handled-correctly/.If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please write to us.If you have any queries regarding this Privacy Policy, or require any additional information or explanation, we will be more than happy to help. Please write to us or email us.HOW TO CONTACT US:If you want to request information, please email or write to:Simon GillespieData Protection CoordinatorSimon Gillespie Ltd104 New Bond StreetLondonW1S 1SUDate updated: 25.5.18
